迎著風
Brace the wind.
陛下  光之王已經履行了承諾
The lord of light has made good on his promise, my king.
他的火焰已將冰雪消融
His fires have melted the snows away.
前路暢通無阻
The way ahead is clear.
我們進軍臨冬城
We ride for Winterfell.
您將一舉奪下它
And you will take it.
光之王讓我看到波頓的旗幟熊熊燃燒
The lord has shown me Bolton Banners burning.
您將得到本應屬于您的東西
You will receive what is yours by right.
陛下
Your grace.
準備行軍
Prepare to form up.
陛下
Your grace.
講
Tell me.
士卒  黎明前逃走了很多
The men, many deserted before dawn.
有多少
How many?
將近半數
Nearly half.
所有傭兵和全部的馬匹
All the sellswords with all the horses.
陛下
Your grace.
盡管說  總不會比兵變更糟
Speak up. Can't be worse than mutiny.
把她放下來
Cut her down.
陛下
Your grace.
有人看到梅莉珊卓女士騎馬出了營地
The lady Melisandre was just seen riding out of camp.
傳令集合  準備行軍
Get the men into marching formation.
向臨冬城進發
On to Winterfell.
他雙手一揚
He raised his hands
它們一下子都站了起來
and they all stood up at once.
成千上萬  世界上最龐大的軍隊
Tens of thousands of them. The biggest army in the world.
你打算怎么做
So what are you gonna do?
我打算祈禱它們別學會爬長城
I'm gonna hope they don't learn how to climb the Wall.
但是龍晶...
But the dragonglass...
沒人拿得回來了
No one's ever getting that back now.
反正也是杯水車薪
It wouldn't have mattered anyway.
除非我們有座龍晶山
Not unless we had a mountain of it.
可你殺死了一個異鬼
But you killed a white walker.
用的是長爪
With Longclaw.
我眼見鋼斧在他們面前如玻璃般粉碎
I saw them shatter steel axes like they were glass.
-可長爪...  -是瓦雷利亞鋼
- But Longclaw... - is Valyrian steel.
七國上下還有多少把瓦雷利亞鋼劍
How many Valyrian steel swords are left in the Seven Kingdoms?
遠遠不夠
Not enough.
有史以來第一個犧牲誓言兄弟性命
The first Lord Commander in history to sacrifice
去救野人的總司令
the lives of sworn brothers to save the lives of wildlings.
跟黑城堡最遭憎恨的人做朋友感覺如何
How's it feel to be friends with the most hated man in Castle Black?
我剛到這兒你就是我朋友了
You were friends with me when I first came here.
那時候可沒什么人喜歡我
And I wasn't winning any elections back then.
那么這一杯敬我們
Here's to us, then.
但憑他們嘲笑吧
Long may they sneer.
怎么了
What?
我想求你一件事
I wanted to ask you something.
求你為我做件事
To ask something of you.
送我  吉莉和孩子去舊鎮
Send me, Gilly, and the baby to Oldtown
讓我受訓成為學士
so I can become a maester.
那才是我天生該做的事  不是打仗
That's what I'm meant to be. Not this.
這里需要你  山姆
I need you here, Sam.
要是你走了  還有誰能給我可信的忠告
If you leave, who's left to give me advice I trust?
還有艾迪啊
Well, there's Edd.
我成為學士對你更有用
I'd be more use to you as a maester.
對大家都更有用  伊蒙學士不在了
More use to everyone now that Maester Aemon is gone.
學城有世界上最大的圖書館
The Citadel has the world's greatest library.
我會學習歷史
I'll learn about history,
策略  醫術
strategy, healing.
還有其他知識
And other things,
到時候用得上的
things that will help when--
那些東西來的時候
when they come.
如果吉莉留在這里  她會死的
If Gilly stays here, then she'll die.
她以我的名字命名的孩子也會死
And the baby that she named after me will die.
我也會死  為了保護他們
And I'll end up dying, too, trying to protect them.
那樣的話  我在世上最后所見
Which means that the last thing that I'll see in this world
將是我沒能保護他們時她的眼神
will be the look in her eyes when I fail them.
我寧愿面對一千異鬼  也不愿見到那一幕
And I'd rather see a thousand white walkers than see that.
謝謝你
Thank you.
你知道學城也會讓你發誓不近女色
You know that the Citadel will make you swear off women, too.
他們可以試啊
Oh, they'll bloody try.
-山姆  -怎么啦
- Sam. - What?
山姆
Sam.
你那時剛被打了個半死  你是怎么...
You had just been beaten half to death. How did you--
小心翼翼唄
Oh, very carefully.
真高興在末日劫難之時還有人交了好運
I'm glad the end of the world's working out well for someone.
我會回來的
I'll come back.
敬你歸來
To your return.
敬我歸來
To my return.
這邊
Aye, this way.
小姐
My lady!
史坦尼斯
Stannis.
史坦尼斯·拜拉席恩來了  帶著軍隊
Stannis Baratheon is coming. His whole army.
你怎么知道是史坦尼斯
How do you know it's Stannis?
他們舉著烈焰紅心旗
They're carrying his flaming heart banners.
我在黑水河上見過  一輩子也忘不了
From the Blackwater. I'll never forget it.
在這里挖戰壕
Trench here.
距城墻三百碼再挖一道
Another one 300 yards from the castle wall.
讓他們快點兒
Hurry them along.
在兩坡之間挖
Dig between those two rises.
-傳令下去  -我跟你走
- Spread out. - I'm with you.
-弓箭手  -傳令下去
- Archers! - Spread out!
馬上派人出去征收糧草
And send out a foraging party immediately.
日出開始圍攻
Siege begins at sunrise.
不會有圍攻了  陛下
There's not going to be a siege, Your Grace.
我們毫無勝算
We've got no chance!
不要  求你
No, please, please.
波頓還找了女人替他打仗
Bolton has women fighting for him?
我不為波頓家效命
I don't fight for the Boltons.
我是塔斯的布蕾妮
I'm Brienne of Tarth.
我本是藍禮·拜拉席恩的彩虹護衛
I was kingsguard to Renly Baratheon.
那個有你容貌的影子刺殺他時  我也在場
I was there when he was murdered by a shadow with your face.
你使用血魔法殺了他嗎
You murdered him with blood magic?
是的
I did.
以藍禮·拜拉席恩一世
In the name of Renly of house Baratheon, first of his name,
安達爾人和先民的真王
rightful king of the Andals and the First Men,
七國的統治者暨全境守護之名
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms and protector of the realm,
我  塔斯的布蕾妮  判你死刑
I, Brienne of Tarth, sentence you to die.
你可有遺言
Do you have any last words?
來吧  履行你的職責
Go on, do your duty.
看來我們的活兒干完了
Looks like we're done here.
我投降  我投降
I surrender! I surrender!
我接受你的投降
And I accept your surrender.
我們回去吧
Let's head back.
我妻子一定孤單了
My wife must be lonely.
夫人
My lady.
我來送您回房間去
I've come to escort you back to your chamber.
跟她走吧  拜托
Go with her, please.
我知道拉姆斯的本性
I know what Ramsay is.
我知道他會怎么待我
I know what he'll do to me.
如果注定要死
If I'm going to die,
就讓我趁還沒完全失卻本心前死掉
let it happen while there's still some of me left.
死
Die?
誰說你要死了
Who said anything about dying?
你不能死
You can't die.
你父親是北境守護
Your father was Warden of the North.
拉姆斯需要你
Ramsay needs you.
不過他應該不需要完整的你
Though I suppose he doesn't need all of you.
只需要為他生育子嗣的那些部分
Just the parts he'll use to make his heir,
等你生了一兩個兒子  就沒有使用價值了
until you've given him a boy or two and he's finished using them.
然后怎么處置那些部分  他自有好點子呢
Then he's got incredible plans for those parts.
所以  我們是等他回來
So, shall we wait for him to come back
還是這就開始
or should we begin now?
你要我決定嗎
You're leaving it to me?
太好了
Good.
我們開始吧
Let's begin.
臭佬  住手
Reek... stop!
住手
Stop!
打開大門
Open the gate!
他回來了
He's coming back.
看來我有的忙活了
I can see I have my work cut out for me.
你倆  出去
You two, out.
你是我名單上的第一個
You were the first person on my list, you know.
你殺了西利歐·佛瑞爾  記得他嗎
For killing Syrio Forel. Remember him?
很可能不記得了
Probably not.
還有其他幾個人
I've gotten a few of the others.
千面之神偷走了幾個
The many-faced god stole a few more from me.
但他把你留給我  我很高興
But I'm glad he left me you.
你知道我是誰嗎
Do you know who I am?
我聽不到
I can't hear you.
你知道我是誰
You know who I am.
我是艾莉亞·史塔克
I'm Arya Stark.
你知道你是誰嗎
Do you know who you are?
你是無名之輩
You're no one.
你什么也不是
You're nothing.
女孩奪走了一條命
A girl has taken a life.
不該奪的命
The wrong life.
我說對了
I was right about her.
是啊
You were.
你還沒準備好
You're not ready.
根本沒準備好
Not at all.
那人的命不該由你取
That man's life was not yours to take.
女孩偷了千面之神的東西
A girl stole from the many-faced god.
如今債已欠下
Now a debt is owed.
只有死亡能還人命債
Only death can pay for life.
不要
No! No!
不要  你不能死  別死啊
No, you... don't die! Don't die!
你為什么要哭
Why are you crying?
他是我朋友
He was my friend.
不  他不是  你沒聽他說什么嗎
No, he wasn't. Didn't you listen to him?
他是無名之輩
He was no one.
可如果你是...
But if you're...
這是誰
Who's this?
無名之輩
No one at all.
女孩也該做無名之輩
Just as a girl should have been
才能拿走大廳里的臉
before she took a face from the hall.
臉是給無名之輩的
The faces are for no one.
而你仍是有名之人
You are still someone.
對于有名之人
And to someone,
臉與毒藥無異
the faces are as good as poison.
我看不到了
I can't see.
怎么回事
What's happening?
What's happening?!
-祝你返鄉順利  -謝謝
- I wish you a safe journey home. - Thank you.
原諒我  孩子
Forgive me, child.
我衷心祝你幸福快樂
I wish you all the happiness in the world.
或許我改日會來看你
Maybe I'll come visit you sometime.
或許我會去看你
Maybe I'll come visit you.
別等太久
Don't wait too long.
家里還有個貴婦人等著我娶
Got a noblewoman to marry back home.
你想要個清白的姑娘
You want a good girl,
但也缺不了壞壞的小婊子
but you need the bad pussy.
準備好了就出發  大人
Whenever you're ready, my lord.
別再把它弄丟了
Try not to lose it this time.
我再也不會取下來了
I'll never take it off again.
我知道你并不希望離開多恩
I know you didn't want to leave Dorne,
但我很高興你能回家
but I'm glad you're coming home.
你母親迫切地想要見你
Your mother's desperate to see you.
很高興崔斯丹與我們同行
I'm glad Trystane is coming with us.
他看上去是個好小子
He seems like a nice boy.
你很幸運
You're lucky.
指定的婚姻很少能...
Arranged marriages are rarely so--
指得這么好
so well arranged.
你覺得母親會喜歡他嗎
Do you think mother will like him?
只要她看到你幸福  我相信她會的
If she sees you're happy, I'm sure she will.
你真的這么想
You really believe that?
你想想  除了她的孩子們
Have you ever known your mother to like anyone
你母親還喜歡過誰
aside from her children?
她喜歡你
She likes you.
這我可不敢肯定
I'm not so sure about that.
聽著
Listen...
我想告訴你一件事
There's something I wanted to tell you.
很久以前就應該告訴你了
Something I should have told you long ago.
怎么說呢
So...
既然你如今的閱歷也廣了些
Now that you've seen more of the world,
想必也知道世事有多復雜
you've learned how complicated things can be,
人心有多難測
people can be.
蘭尼斯特家和馬泰爾家多年來相互仇視
The Lannisters and the Martells have hated each other for years,
但你卻與崔斯丹墜入愛河
but you've fallen in love with Trystane.
這是機緣巧合  真的  這可能性多小啊
It was an accident, really. I mean, what were the chances?
你碰巧愛上了那個
You happen to fall in love with the man
指給你的男人
you were assigned to marry?
我想說的是...
My point is...
我們無法選擇自己所愛的人
We don't choose whom we love.
這只是...
It just, well--
我們不能自持
It's beyond our control.
-我真像個傻瓜  -不  沒有的事
- I sound like an idiot. - No, you don't.
我想說的是...我想表達
What I'm trying to say-- what I'm trying
卻又難以啟齒的是...
and failing to say--
我知道你想說什么
I know what you're trying to say.
不  恐怕你不懂
No, I'm afraid you don't.
我懂
I do.
我都知道
I know.
你和母親的事
About you and mother.
我想我內心深處早就知道了
I think a part of me always knew.
并且  我很慶幸
And I'm glad.
我很慶幸你是我的父親
I'm glad that you're my father.
彌賽菈
Myrcella?
彌賽菈  彌賽菈
Myrcella? Myrcella?
你們愛她  不是嗎
You love her, don't you?
怎么能不愛她
How could you not?
當然你們的愛都是無望的
Of course it's hopeless for the both of you.
一個是斗技場的傭兵  一個是不名譽的騎士
A sellsword from the fighting pits, a disgraced knight.
誰都不適合成為女王的好夫君
Neither one of you is fit consort for a queen.
但我們誰沒有奢求一份錯位的愛情呢
But we always want the wrong woman.
他總是這么喜歡廢話嗎
Does he always talk so much?
安達爾人喬拉
Jorah the Andal.
灰蟲子
Torgo Nudho.
他不該在這兒
He should not be here.
沒錯  但他就在這兒
No, but he is.
女王已下令將他逐出城外
Our queen ordered him exiled from city.
若不是有他  女王就死了
Our queen would be dead if not for him.
真的  而我  如果不是這個...
小個子
侏儒
應該是這個詞
不好意思
我的瓦雷利亞語有點森蘇
有點生疏
生疏  謝謝你
Punila. Thank you.
我很遺憾
I am sorry.
當時我不在場  不能為女王而戰
Sorry I not there to fight for our queen.
你錯過了一場精彩的斗毆
You missed a good scrap.
這些都不重要了
None of that matters now.
我們在這兒自怨自艾
The longer we sit here bantering,
丹妮莉絲還困在蠻荒之地遭罪
the longer Daenerys is out there in the wilderness.
他說的沒錯  龍飛向北邊
He's right. The dragon headed north.
如果我們要找她  就得往北走
If we're going to find her, that's where we'll have to go.
"我們"
We?
你是蘭尼斯特
You're a Lannister.
女王力求推翻你們家族的統治
The queen intends to remove your family from power.
而我要助她得償所愿
And I intend to help her do it.
你來這兒才幾天
You've been here for how many days now?
我為她而戰已有多年
I've fought for her for years.
最早的時候她不比孩子大多少
Since she was little more than a child.
-你背叛過她  -說話小心點
- You betrayed her. - Careful now.
她放逐了你  兩次  如果我沒記錯的話
And she exiled you. Twice, I believe.
第二次還是多虧了你呢
The second time thanks to you.
別把你犯下的罪行歸咎到我頭上  莫爾蒙
Don't blame me for your crimes, Mormont.
他說的對  女王放逐了喬拉
He's right. Our queen exiled Jorah.
但他說的也沒錯  喬拉救過她的命
And he's right. Jorah saved her life.
或許女王對他的看法已經有所改變了
Perhaps she feels differently about him now.
或許不然  但我們要問過她才會知道
Perhaps not. The only way we'll know is if we ask her.
好吧  或許他可以跟我們一起
Fine, fine. I suppose he can join us.
只要他答應別趁我睡覺時殺了我就行
Just as long as he promises not to kill me in my sleep.
如果我要殺你  你的眼睛一定睜著
If I ever kill you, your eyes will be wide open.
恕我直言  我們為何要帶上你
Forgive me, but why would we bring you?
-什么  -你在野外追蹤過野獸嗎
- Pardon me? - Have you ever tracked animals in the wilderness?
那倒沒有  但我還有別的實用技能
Not precisely, but I have other skills that would be useful.
你能戰斗嗎
Can you fight?
我戰斗過
I have fought.
我沒有自稱是偉大的戰士
I don't claim to be a great warrior.
你騎術如何
Are you good on a horse?
馬馬虎虎
Middling.
所以你基本上只會耍嘴皮子
So mainly you talk.
還會喝酒  我都活這么久了
And drink. I've survived so far.
我對此深為佩服  但這次遠征要你無用
Which I respect, but you would not help us on this expedition.
你留在彌林卻可以幫助我們
You would help us here in Meereen, though.
我們都沒有治理城邦的經驗
None of us have experience governing a city
除了他
except for him.
你不是想向女王證明自己的價值嗎
You want to prove your value to the queen?
就在彌林證明吧
Prove it right here in Meereen.
他是個連當地語言都說不利索的異邦侏儒
He's a foreign dwarf that barely speaks the language.
彌林人憑什么聽他的
Why would the Meereenese listen to him?
他們不聽他的
They wouldn't.
他們會聽灰蟲子的
They will listen to Grey Worm.
我要和你們同去
I'll come with you.
我要找到女王
I'll find our queen.
-你的身體狀況還不能出行  -我可以
- You are not strong enough to go anywhere. - I am.
他可以  他是我見過的最有種的閹人
He is. He's the toughest man with no balls I ever met.
可你還是不能去
But you still can't go.
這里的人民信任你
The people believe in you.
他們知道你是女王的代言人
They know you speak for the queen.
沒錯
It's true.
只有無垢者能維持彌林的和平
Only the unsullied can keep the peace in Meereen.
如果你離開
If you leave,
彌林肯定一分為二  自相殘殺
half this city will consume the other half.
還有彌桑黛
And Missandei.
女王最信任的人是彌桑黛
Our queen trusts no one more than Missandei.
肯定不是我
Certainly not me.
女王最親近的密友
The queen's closest confidante,
無垢者的指揮官
the commander of the unsullied,
以及來自異邦的疤臉侏儒
and a foreign dwarf with a scarred face.
祝你們好運  我的朋友們
Good fortune, my friends.
彌林古老而榮耀
Meereen is ancient and glorious.
盡量別毀了她
Try not to ruin her.
看來只有你我二人了  安達爾人喬拉
Looks like it's you and me, Jorah the Andal.
我們去找幾匹好馬
Let's find some good horses.
路上還有說不完的話呢
We have so much to talk about.
你好啊  老朋友
Hello, old friend.
我還以為我們在一起很快樂
I thought we were so happy together
結果你拋棄了我
until you abandoned me.
我猜沒必要問你是怎么找到我的
I suppose there's no point asking how you found me.
西邊的鳥兒會唱歌  東邊的鳥兒也會唱
The birds sing in the west, the birds sing in the east,
只要你懂得如何聆聽
if one knows how to listen.
聽說你已經獲得了龍之母的垂青
They tell me you've already found favor with the mother of dragons.
怎么說呢  她沒有處決我
Well, she didn't execute me,
算是開了個好頭
so that's a promising start.
現在英雄們去找她了
Now the heroes are off to find her
而我困守在此
and I'm stuck here
意欲挽救本城于內戰邊緣
trying to placate a city on the brink of civil war.
老朋友有什么建議給我嗎
Any advice for an old comrade?
情報是關鍵
Information is the key.
你需要了解敵人的優勢和策略
You need to learn your enemy's strengths and strategies.
你需要知曉哪位朋友笑里藏刀
You need to learn which of your friends are not your friends.
但愿我認識一個觸角無所不至的能人
If only I knew someone with a vast network of spies.
但愿如此
If only.
一座雄偉的古城
A grand old city
因暴力  腐敗和欺騙而瀕臨崩潰
choking on violence, corruption, and deceit.
誰有經驗馴服
Who could possibly have any experience
如此巨大而蠢笨的野獸呢
managing such a massive, ungainly beast?
我真心想念你
I did miss you.
噢  我知道
Oh, I know.
我們必須回家
We have to go home.
可憐又可愛的孩子
Oh, my poor, sweet thing.
疼嗎
Does it hurt?
我們必須回家
We have to go home.
卓耿
Drogon.
你能帶我回彌林嗎
Can you take me back to Meereen?
你帶我飛了多遠
How far did you carry me?
卓耿  我們得回去
Drogon, we need to return.
我的人民需要我
My people need me.
這里沒有食物
Well, there's no food.
你至少給我們捕些晚飯回來啊
At the very least, you could hunt us some supper.
懺悔
Confess.
我有罪
I have sinned.
我現在知道了
I see that now.
我怎會糊涂那么久
How can I have been so blind for so long?
我想清潔自己
I want to be clean again.
我想獲得赦免
I want absolution.
老嫗高舉金燈來到我面前
The Crone came to me with her lamp raised high.
讓沐浴圣光的...
And by its holy light--
您想懺悔
You wish to make a confession?
我懺悔之后  能否放了我
Once I've confessed, will I be free?
對陛下的處置將視陛下的罪行而定
Your grace will be dealt with according to her sins.
那么愿圣母慈悲
The Mother have mercy, then.
我懺悔  我在婚外出軌
I lay with a man outside the bonds of marriage. I confess.
跟誰
Name him.
藍賽爾·蘭尼斯特
Lancel Lannister.
您的堂弟  國王的侍從
Your cousin and the king's squire.
-我那時孤單害怕  -您有丈夫
- I was lonely and afraid. - You had a husband.
一個成天狎妓的丈夫...
A husband off whoring every chance he--
他的罪無法抵消您的罪
His sins do not pardon your own.
愿諸神寬恕我
May the gods forgive me.
其他男人呢
Other men?
沒有了
No.
沒有別人了嗎
No others?
沒有了
No.
在諸神面前撒謊可是大罪
Speaking falsehoods before the gods is a great crime.
您明白吧
You understand this?
明白
I do.
有人說您的孩子
There are those that say your children
并非您與勞勃國王所生
were not fathered by King Robert,
而是通奸亂倫的孽種
that they are bastards born of incest and adultery.
謊言
A lie.
史坦尼斯·拜拉席恩的無恥謊言
A lie from the lips of Stannis Baratheon.
他妄圖篡奪鐵王座
He wants the throne,
但他哥哥的孩子阻礙他即位
but his brother's children stand in his way.
所以他污蔑他們是野種
So he claims they are not his brother's.
那個混蛋
That filth.
根本就是一派胡言
There is not one shred of truth to it.
我否認
I deny it.
很好
Good.
但這些罪名極為嚴重
But these are terrible charges.
七國子民必須知道真相
And the realm must know the truth of them.
若陛下所言非虛
If Your Grace has given honest testimony,
審判必將還您清白
your trial will prove your innocence.
審判  我已經懺悔了
Trial? I have confessed.
只是其中一項罪名
To a single sin.
其余的您都否認了
Others you have denied.
審判將辨明真偽
Your trial will separate the truths from the falsehoods.
謹遵總主教大人的英明裁斷
I bow to the wisdom of your high holiness.
但我可否請求
But if I might beg
圣母稍示慈悲
for just one drop of the Mother's Mercy.
我都不知多久
I haven't seen my son--
沒見過我的兒子了
I don't know how long it's been.
我要見見他  求您了
I need to see him, please.
您已踏出了回歸正途的第一步
You have taken the first step on the path back to righteousness.
有鑒于此
In light of this,
我允許您回到紅堡
I will permit you to return to the Red Keep.
謝謝您
Thank you.
圣母慈悲
The Mother is merciful.
您應當感謝她
It is her you should thank.
我會的  我會的
I will. I will.
我發誓  我必將日夜感激
I swear it, day and night.
很好
Good.
我可以走了嗎
Am I free to go?
待你贖罪之后
After your atonement.
贖罪
My atonement?
諸位面前之罪人
A sinner comes before you.
是蘭尼斯特家的瑟曦
Cersei of House Lannister.
托曼國王陛下的生母
Mother to His Grace King Tommen.
勞勃國王陛下的遺孀
Widow of His Grace King Robert.
她承認犯下欺騙和亂倫的大罪
She has committed the acts of falsehood and fornication.
罪人業已懺悔
She has confessed her sins
并祈求寬恕
and begged for forgiveness.
為表示悔改
To demonstrate her repentance,
罪人愿意棄去一切自尊與偽裝
she will cast aside all pride, all artifice,
將諸神創造她的原本模樣
and present herself as the gods made her
示與你等
to you,
全城的善男信女
The good people of the city.
罪人攜莊嚴誠懇之心意而來
She comes before you with a solemn heart,
袒露胸懷
shorn of secrets,
在諸神與世人面前赤裸身體
naked before the eyes of gods and men...
踏上贖罪之旅
to make her walk of atonement.
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
恥辱
Shame.
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
恥辱
Shame.
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
恥辱
Shame.
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
shame. Shame.
恥辱
Shame.
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
恥辱
Shame.
-騷屄  -恥辱
- Cunt! - Shame.
婊子
Whore!
-恥辱  -婊子
- Shame. - Whore!
恥辱
Shame.
-婊子  -婊子
- Whore! - Whore!
恥辱
Shame.
-婊子  -罪人
- Whore! - Sinner!
-恥辱  -蕩婦  姐弟通奸
- Shame. - Bitch! Brother fucker!
-婊子  -恥辱
- Whore! - Shame.
-滾開  -恥辱
- Fuck off! - Shame.
恥辱
Shame.
王家奶頭萬歲  你這個蕩婦
All hail the royal tits. You're a bitch!
恥辱
Shame.
-打她  -婊子
- Get her! - Whore!
-蕩婦  -通奸
- Bitch! - Fucker!
-通奸  -蕩婦
- Fucker! - You bitch!
-恥辱  -騷屄
- Shame. - Cunt!
恥辱
Shame.
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
-姐弟通奸  -蕩婦
- Brother fucker! - Bitch!
我玩過的雞巴只有太后玩過的一半多
I've had half as many cocks as the queen.
-蕩婦  -恥辱
- Bitch! - Shame.
-恥辱  -罪人  -婊子  -淫婦
- Shame. - Sinner! - Whore! - Slut!
恥辱
shame.
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
婊子  婊子  婊子
Whore! Whore, whore.
我是蘭尼斯特  舔我啊
I'm a Lannister. Suck me off!
-來舔我  蕩婦  -退后
- Suck me off, you bitch! - Back!
-婊子  -恥辱
- Whore! - Shame.
恥辱
shame.
婊子
Whore!
婊子  婊子  婊子
Whore! Whore! Whore!
恥辱  恥辱
shame. Shame.
恥辱
Shame.
shame.
恥辱
Shame.
-蕩婦  蕩婦  -恥辱
- Bitch! Bitch! - Shame.
姐弟通奸
Brother fucker!
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
恥辱
shame.
-婊子  -姐弟通奸
- Whore! - Brother fucker!
-婊子  -恥辱
- Whore! - Shame.
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
恥辱
shame.
Shame.
恥辱
shame.
-恥辱  -通奸
- Shame. - Fucker!
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
恥辱
shame.
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
shame. Shame.
恥辱
Shame.
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
恥辱
Shame.
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
恥辱
Shame.
恥辱  恥辱
Shame. Shame.
恥辱
Shame.
陛下
Your grace.
您能回來真是太好了
It's good to have you back.
來
Come.
我們送您進去
We'll take you inside.
我需要檢查一下您的腳
I need to have a look at those feet.
我可有榮幸
May I have the honor of
向您介紹御林鐵衛的新成員
presenting the newest member of the kingsguard?
陛下明鑒  他發下了神圣的靜默誓言
If it please your grace, he has taken a holy vow of silence.
他發誓  在殺掉陛下所有敵人
He has sworn that he will not speak
將罪惡驅離王國以前
until all his grace's enemies are dead
決不開口
and evil has been driven from the realm.
是誰來幫你  是史坦尼斯
Who came to your aid? Stannis.
現在他需要你
Now he needs you.
我們人手不足  無法扭轉局勢
We don't have enough men to make any difference.
野人們能扭轉局勢
The wildlings will make a difference.
野人們絕不會為史坦尼斯效命
The wildlings will never fight for Stannis.
-我告訴過他  -你救了他們的小命
- I told him before. - You saved their bloody lives.
如果他們打算住在七國之內
If they're gonna live in the Seven Kingdoms,
受我們的長城保護  他們就該自己爭取
safe behind our Wall, they ought to fight for the damn place.
-這不是他們的戰爭  -開門
- It's not their fight. - Open the gates!
史坦尼斯呢
Stannis?
希琳公主呢
Shireen? The princess?
總司令大人
Lord Commander.
您帶回來的一個野人
It's one of the wildlings you brought back.
說他知道您叔叔班揚
Says he knows your uncle Benjen.
說他還活著
Says he's still alive.
你確定他說的就是班揚
Are you sure he's talking about Benjen?
他說那人是首席游騎兵
Said he was first ranger.
說他知道去哪里找到那人
Said he knows where to find him.
有人說看到你叔叔上個滿月在艱難屯
Man says he saw your uncle at Hardhome at the last full moon.
-可能說謊  -有可能
- Could be lying. - Could be.
有辦法找出真相
There are ways to find out.
-他人呢  -那邊
- Where is he? - Over there.
叛徒
為了守夜人
For the watch.
for the watch.
奧利
Olly...
為了守夜人
For the watch.
本字幕首發于字幕組網站
www.ZiMuZu.tv 歡迎交流
翻譯  草草 送小孩 瀟湘月影
翻譯  Silmar 白月 泰斯
校對  Silmar 泰斯  顧問  屈暢(ccxx)
時間軸  崽豬 加森 全家筒 aaaBao
后期 吉吉  總監 泰斯·雪諾
打開微信   掃描左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    ustvboom
了解最新影視字幕發布信息
改編自《冰與火之歌》
原著 喬治·R·R·馬丁
權力的游戲
第五季 第十集